<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interactive Multimedia Course Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://shajadi.com/im/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Interactive Multimedia Course Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://shajadi.com/im/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 1</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab1/</guid>
      <description>1 Definitions a. HTML: stands for Hypertext Markup Language that is a mark up language and not a programming language and we can build web pages and we can import stylesheet and javascript too
b. CSS: stands for Cascading Style Sheet is a markup language to writing the style of a web page and it can be imported and written directly in html files
c. Javascript: is a programming language that is weakly typed and interpreted developed to run in web browsers because of being fast and light, currently we can run js in server side with technologies like nodejs too, all the modern browsers support javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 2</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:16:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab2/</guid>
      <description>1 RWD  What is the purpose of the RWD? Why it is used? How things are done before RWD? What is the difference?
Responsive web design (RWD) is the way of writing web application with the help of mostly css technology to make the web page responsive to different windows size and show properly in for example big screen, normal desktop screen, tablet and mobile phone, with responsive design element position changes on different screen size so navigating the web page is easier and usage of space on the page is more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 3</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:16:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab3/</guid>
      <description>1 Web Sockets Link
 What happens if you send a message: ”LOGO”?
It returns the html code of logo
  2 Local Storage Link
3 Audio element Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 4</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:16:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab4/</guid>
      <description>1 Very simple draw application Link
2 Simple game Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 5</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:16:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab5/</guid>
      <description>1 Getting familiar with jQuery  What you can do with the jQuery?
jQuery is a famous javascript library that loads in clients browsers and facilitate developing a web application with javascript, its open source
 How it can help you as web developer?
It has internal functions and selectors for working with DOM and html and also working with Json and it makes programming the logic part of application easy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 6</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:16:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/im/labs/lab6/</guid>
      <description>1 Flickr photo wall Link
2 Node.js &amp;amp; Heroku Tutorial Heroku App</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>